toward a level to cultivate good and to cleanse one's mind
达到培养善良和清洁思想的水平
this is the teaching of the buddha meditation is scientifically proven
这是佛经冥想的教学已被科学证明
doubt many half benefits like reduced and righty and the caller
怀疑许多好处，例如减少和正确以及来电者
emotionally half yes this is great he if we see many people struggling with
在情感上一半是，这很棒，如果我们看到很多人都在挣扎
incorporating meditation part your teams even though it takes
将冥想纳入您的团队，即使这需要花费
an effort to that now it there is one thing it play that doesn't like
现在要做的事情是它玩的一件事不喜欢
meditation et al this is the mind in this video alex plein
冥想等，这是这段视频的思想alex plein
where the mind 'is called meditation [Music]
心灵被称为冥想的地方[音乐]
for both check mark christien for your support to peter jan apc this and it
为两个复选标记christien提供支持，以支持Peter Jan apc this and it
helps me to continue this project as he who lives after that experienced with it
帮助我继续这个项目，因为他在那之后经历了
parents has too much trouble meditating whenever they won't be
父母无论何时都不愿意打坐时，都会遇到很多麻烦
customized portal karvink in mind sb came dominant 'all over the average
考虑到sb的定制门户karvink占据了主导地位
joe but yourself and to dabble oft and experience as an mind
乔，但你自己，常常哭泣，心存经验
talking about lee active eager to solve puzzles analysis dear fans and chocolate
谈论lee积极渴望解决难题分析亲爱的粉丝和巧克力
future possibilities no matter or is purple with night
未来的可能性，无论是夜晚还是紫色
the mind 'is a pressure chair what win it out of control it can do more
头脑'是压力椅子，什么会使它失去控制，它可以做得更多
destructive monster aswell the quality of false is as authentic as
破坏性的怪物以及假的质量与
imotions earth consistently soft sm brother and stew philosopher
imotions地球始终如一的软sm兄弟和炖哲学家
marcus aurelius budget the position think about the chairman the quality of your
marcus aurelius预算职位考虑主席的质量
mind your soul takes on the color of your photos and quote
介意你的灵魂承担你照片的色彩和报价
negative photos most likely scarcer grace was the photos most likely
负照片极有可能是稀缺的恩典
kas laughter it's not and came and at people that ar and
笑声不是，然后来了，对着那些人和
the constants time or negative ranking end up being de presto ranchers this
常数时间或负排名最终成为de presto ranchers this
makes overthinking dangerous because drivers come along and education and that of
过度思考使危险变得危险，因为驾驶员进来并接受教育，
killing them even the ancient practice of meditation
甚至杀死他们古老的冥想习惯
cruise to be actor for the restless mind de boer disco search mind on my
巡航成为不安的心的演员布尔迪斯科搜寻我的心
mind because it tends to jump from industry
介意，因为它往往会跳出行业
grunge currently western healthcare he speak on
垃圾目前西方医疗保健，他谈到
technology the benefits of meditation zoey
技术冥想的好处
increasingly sea doctors prescribing add to my passions the most came and form
越来越多的海上医生开出处方，使我的激情更加浓厚
from meditation is brad meditation is very simple reilly
从冥想开始，布拉德冥想非常简单
you just sit down or lay down and watch the graph you can focus on how to grab
您只需坐下或躺下观看图表，您就可以专注于如何抓住
and george jonas trails of how it feels on the along and bella and john as if focus
和乔治·乔纳斯（George Jonas）沿途以及贝拉（Bella）和约翰（John）的感受
at the moments between the in and tagged brad the mind wants to do anything to die
在in和标记的brad之间的时刻，头脑想做任何事情死掉
virtual tension tour de force at producers and one that
对生产者的虚拟张力之旅，
If your focus retention back happens, it happens
如果您的焦点保留发生了，那就发生了
again you can bring back your attention to your breath
再次，您可以将注意力重新吸引到您的呼吸上
the essence of this practice is that you don't engage with your thinking mind but
这种做法的本质是，您不参与思考，但是
just let it be watched the forthcoming go
只是让它被注视即将到来
liken claus in the sky by focusing your attention to grab you some yourself to
通过集中注意力吸引您自己来像天空中的克劳斯
something that is not your franking practice is that simple
那不是您的坦率做法就是如此简单
incredibly difficult for many over fingers to
许多手指难以置信的困难
actually do it on a regular basis experience that the
实际上定期进行
more active my mind s class now and then do it
时不时地提高我的思维能力
specially in the exercise after a busy day with lots of distractions my
特别是在忙碌了一天之后，分心的运动中
thinking is morning show and tap their savior scroll down the
思维是早间表演，然后点击他们的救星向下滚动
facebook-feed or watch pointless videos on youtube and sitting down for 20
Facebook馈送或在youtube上观看无意义的视频并坐下20
minutes watching my grab this doesn't make sense
分钟看着我的抓紧这是没有意义的
picas checking social media and getting your videos is even more time for a more
picas检查社交媒体并获取视频的时间更多，更多
avatar the mind while watching the graph gifs the mind and break so was the
在观看图形时化身为gif的头脑和休息，所以是
problem the buddha also noticed that it's
问题佛陀也注意到
difficult to tame the mind a quote wonderful and the aim is to
难以驯服一个引人入胜的报价，目的是
secure the mind zo the photo showed you even swift and
确保照片的安全，甚至可以使您迅速
seeing what ever and designer at end mind bring happiness and quote de
看到曾经和最终设计师带来的快乐并引用de
struggle is that the mind and notes and meditation is good for you is so one
挣扎是思想，笔记和冥想对你有好处，所以
mind dat 1000 want to stop thinking this part of the mind 1000 likes
思维dat 1000想要停止思考思维的这一部分1000喜欢
meditation effect it's called set simply because
冥想效果之所以称为集合，是因为
meditation should use this family brewers thinking
冥想应该利用这个家庭酿酒者的思想
now you can make distinctions between mental
现在您可以区分精神
picoult dialekten kool behavior therapy that is
Picoult Dialekten Kool行为疗法
used to treat should always be the distinguishinges 3 mental
用于治疗疾病的方法可区分3种精神疾病
reasonable might die emotional mind and the weiss mind the
理性可能会使情感的头脑和维斯的头脑丧命
emotional mind 'is a man's logic as time is dominated by emotions and
情感的思想是男人的逻辑，因为时间受情感和情感的支配。
creates a very subjective you of reality through reasonable mind on a
通过理性的思维在现实中创造出一个非常主观的现实你
already based on fact and a great app planning and analyzing both of these
已经基于事实和出色的应用计划，并且对这两项进行了分析
however can be out of control the weiss mind is a healthy balance
然而，维斯的思想可能会失控，这是一个健康的平衡
between the two is the part that knows what is best for
两者之间是知道最适合什么的部分
you in a state or morally mourn the little
你处在某种状态或在道德上哀悼一点
voice that knows that in mind meter wide is coming from the white
知道心宽的声音来自白色
that emotionally might have ever was the be completely and nurse and free links
在情感上可能曾经是完全和护士以及自由的联系
no matter even senger letter oh listen and ruiz noble mind
甚至信使信哦，听着，鲁伊斯高尚的心
wants to solve the future problems and kind of old press events and xciting it
想要解决未来的问题和旧的新闻事件并对其进行引用
I myself do the stronger reasonable and emotional my
我自己会尽自己的合理和情感做自己的事
car de harder and the get to actually listen
更加努力的去真正地倾听
to de maïs maïs voice meditation is his effort to time the mind
对demaïsmaïs的声音冥想是他努力思考的时间
even though it a thousand because who thinks is why so difficult to me 'time
即使是一千，因为谁认为这就是为什么我对我这么难'的时间
for there are some bases its goal against the settlement the one
因为它有一些针对反对和解的目标
mind 'in joyce doing luckily there so i support riders that
介意在乔伊斯幸运地在那里做，所以我支持车手
knows best the key is listening to add thank you for watching
最了解的关键是聆听添加感谢您的观看
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐] [掌声]
her
她